

Popova Yevheniia Front-end developer

+38 (050) 214 63 20 Kharkiv, Ukraine

popovaevg18@gmail.com

LinkedIn GitHub

Skype: jenia19972013

About:

I have 5,5 years of university experience in software development; more than 2 years of experience as front-end developer (more than 2 years of experience in HTML, CSS; more than 1 year of experience in JavaScript); 5 refresher courses, webinars, trainings.

You need me, if you want to grow your company. You will acquire responsible, diligent specialist and, at the same time, friendly, cheerful person in your team.

You need me, because I have a great desire to develop, I'm very motivated, and most importantly, I love what I do!

I will help your company grow by working on your projects. And if you play chess, I will beat you.

Work experience:

2014 – 2019 Course works, bachelor's and master's graduation projects

September 2018 – Front-end developer in Ltd. «Devitis» – development of company's website, development of layouts and the client part of the project

"Automated accounting system marked underground communications"

Automated accounting system marked underground comm

2018 – 2020 Projects for refresher courses

October 2019 – May Freelance Web developer – fix projects

2020

Projects:

- https://popovaevgeniya.github.io/BreakfastWithTiffany/
- https://popovaevgeniya.github.io/Cloth%20and%20fashion/
- https://popovaevgeniya.github.io/Epam/start.html

Skills, knowledge:

Programming HTML 5, CSS 3/SCSS/SASS (responsive, adaptive), JavaScript

languages

Database MySQL

Frameworks Bootstrap, JQuery, React, Redux, React-thunk

CMS WordPress

Methodology BEM

Tools Visual Studio Code, WebStorm, SQL Management Studio

Graphic editors Avocode, Figma, Zeplin, Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop

Version control GIT

system

Package managers Webpack, Gulp

Other OOP, Canvas, Cookie, Web Storages, JSON, AJAX, Flexbox, Grid

English Intermediate

Education:

2014 – 2018 National Aerospace after N.E. Zhukovsky «Kharkiv aviation

institute», Kharkov, Faculty of economics and management

Bachelor degree in software engineering

2018 – 2019 National Aerospace after N.E. Zhukovsky «Kharkiv aviation

institute», Kharkov, Faculty of software engineering and business

Master degree in software engineering

Courses:

2020 Epam "Front-end"

2019 Hillel IT-School "Front-end PRO"

2019 English school "NewTone"

2018 Ukrainian IT-school "Java Script"

2018 Ukrainian IT-school "Front-end: HTML + CSS"

2017 English school "NewTone"

Hobbies:

- Speak English to myself
- · Read books before bed for colorful dreams
- Burn sweets in a gym
- Command a chess army